[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["Mr. Crump"]}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "What did George tell you Trayvon Martin allegedly did to him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "George", "tell", "you", "Trayvon", "Martin", "allegedly", "did", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "What has come out that I can talk about today is that Trayvon Martin somehow snuck up on him and according to Mr. Crump, their own attorney, he was on -- we don't know if this is verifiable information, but he was on the phone with his girlfriend.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "has", "come", "out", "that", "I", "can", "talk", "about", "today", "is", "that", "Trayvon", "Martin", "somehow", "snuck", "up", "on", "him", "and", "according", "to", "Mr.", "Crump", ",", "their", "own", "attorney", ",", "he", "was", "on", "--", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "this", "is", "verifiable", "information", ",", "but", "he", "was", "on", "the", "phone", "with", "his", "girlfriend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "What did George tell you he said?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "George", "tell", "you", "he", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "One of those things.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "those", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Tracy, if you had the chance to speak to George Zimmerman right now, what would you say to him?", "question_tokens": ["Tracy", ",", "if", "you", "had", "the", "chance", "to", "speak", "to", "George", "Zimmerman", "right", "now", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "I'd ask him why did he, in fact, pick out my son.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "ask", "him", "why", "did", "he", ",", "in", "fact", ",", "pick", "out", "my", "son", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sybrina"]}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "And how does he feel about taking my son's life?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "does", "he", "feel", "about", "taking", "my", "son", "'s", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "And Sybrina, many believe that you are suffering perhaps even more now since losing your son by the attempt by some people to assassinate his character, to bring up all this stuff about his behavior at school and so on which portrays him in a very damaging light.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "Sybrina", ",", "many", "believe", "that", "you", "are", "suffering", "perhaps", "even", "more", "now", "since", "losing", "your", "son", "by", "the", "attempt", "by", "some", "people", "to", "assassinate", "his", "character", ",", "to", "bring", "up", "all", "this", "stuff", "about", "his", "behavior", "at", "school", "and", "so", "on", "which", "portrays", "him", "in", "a", "very", "damaging", "light", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "It bothers me as a mother to hear all of those negative things about my son.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "bothers", "me", "as", "a", "mother", "to", "hear", "all", "of", "those", "negative", "things", "about", "my", "son", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "What did you make of what they were saying?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "what", "they", "were", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "You know, I'm a parent.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "parent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "But it's just one of those situations where every parent in America, in the world, would say what -- what happened?", "question_tokens": ["But", "it", "'s", "just", "one", "of", "those", "situations", "where", "every", "parent", "in", "America", ",", "in", "the", "world", ",", "would", "say", "what", "--", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I mean it's really important, it seems to me, that you have to allow the legal process to take its course.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "'s", "really", "important", ",", "it", "seems", "to", "me", ",", "that", "you", "have", "to", "allow", "the", "legal", "process", "to", "take", "its", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wild West"]}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Even if they had a fight, that doesn't give you the right to pull out a gun and shoot him in the street, does it?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "if", "they", "had", "a", "fight", ",", "that", "does", "n't", "give", "you", "the", "right", "to", "pull", "out", "a", "gun", "and", "shoot", "him", "in", "the", "street", ",", "does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "We're bringing back the Wild West.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "bringing", "back", "the", "Wild", "West", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Aware of it?", "question_tokens": ["Aware", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "I experienced it for the first time with the Commodores.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "experienced", "it", "for", "the", "first", "time", "with", "the", "Commodores", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "You understand?", "question_tokens": ["You", "understand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "I understand.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "understand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "ICHIE: Am I moving you?", "question_tokens": ["ICHIE", ":", "Am", "I", "moving", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "You're moving -- because I think about you -- you had all the Commodore stuff, and that's enough for most people.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "moving", "--", "because", "I", "think", "about", "you", "--", "you", "had", "all", "the", "Commodore", "stuff", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "enough", "for", "most", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Is he annoyed?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "annoyed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "``", "JJ", "''", "CC", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "It would be \"Easy\" or \"All Night Long.\"", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "``", "Easy", "''", "or", "``", "All", "Night", "Long", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Are you for real a sensitive, romantic, loving kind of guy?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "for", "real", "a", "sensitive", ",", "romantic", ",", "loving", "kind", "of", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "I am a hopeless romantic.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "a", "hopeless", "romantic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "God, you would ask that question.", "answer_tokens": ["God", ",", "you", "would", "ask", "that", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Do you remember her?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "I do remember.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "remember", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Do I have to say that loud?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "have", "to", "say", "that", "loud", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "And how old was she?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "old", "was", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "And I should say there was one more.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "should", "say", "there", "was", "one", "more", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "In what sense?", "question_tokens": ["In", "what", "sense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Well, you know, you think a little bit more before you say I love you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "think", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "before", "you", "say", "I", "love", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "ORGAN: What have you really learned about love?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "have", "you", "really", "learned", "about", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "That you have to throw yourself into it.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "you", "have", "to", "throw", "yourself", "into", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "How do you do it in your marriage?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "do", "it", "in", "your", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Well, mine's easy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "mine", "'s", "easy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "And do they get on now?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "they", "get", "on", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Oh, no, it's perfect.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "no", ",", "it", "'s", "perfect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Do you sing at these little tribal meetings?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "sing", "at", "these", "little", "tribal", "meetings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Well, you know the answer to that, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", "the", "answer", "to", "that", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Go on.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Never?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Who is the biggest, most romantic sexual singer you've ever deployed?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "the", "biggest", ",", "most", "romantic", "sexual", "singer", "you", "'ve", "ever", "deployed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", ",", "RBS", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Holy cow.", "answer_tokens": ["Holy", "cow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "I mean, Marvin, Marvin did it for me, you understand me?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "Marvin", ",", "Marvin", "did", "it", "for", "me", ",", "you", "understand", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "I think I understand you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "understand", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marvin", "Marvin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Barry White"], "PERSON": ["Smokey Robinson"]}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Have you ever had a Barry White night?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "had", "a", "Barry", "White", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Barry White and Smokey Robinson.", "answer_tokens": ["Barry", "White", "and", "Smokey", "Robinson", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Barry White"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "You know what I'm saying?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "You understand?", "question_tokens": ["You", "understand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "I understand.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "understand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Do you understand that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "ICHIE: I understand it.", "answer_tokens": ["ICHIE", ":", "I", "understand", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "You like that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "It was better than mine.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "better", "than", "mine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "And what does the pressure of performance become like when you're going through that deterioration?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "does", "the", "pressure", "of", "performance", "become", "like", "when", "you", "'re", "going", "through", "that", "deterioration", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "You are going through what we call panic.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", "going", "through", "what", "we", "call", "panic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "``", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "''", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "``", "RB", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Is that what you call it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "call", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "You could actually sell sheet music so you know we took over \"Endless Love,\" \"Hello,\" \"Truly.\"", "answer_tokens": ["You", "could", "actually", "sell", "sheet", "music", "so", "you", "know", "we", "took", "over", "``", "Endless", "Love", ",", "''", "``", "Hello", ",", "''", "``", "Truly", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "It's -- \"Tuskegee,\" right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "``", "Tuskegee", ",", "''", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Tuskegee.", "answer_tokens": ["Tuskegee", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "VBD", ",", "``", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "You just did a brilliant impression in the break there from the \"We are the World\" video where all these big stars got to sing one line and I said who sang the best line?", "question_tokens": ["You", "just", "did", "a", "brilliant", "impression", "in", "the", "break", "there", "from", "the", "``", "We", "are", "the", "World", "''", "video", "where", "all", "these", "big", "stars", "got", "to", "sing", "one", "line", "and", "I", "said", "who", "sang", "the", "best", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "''", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "NN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "And the one that I love the most was, \"There's a choice we're making.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "the", "one", "that", "I", "love", "the", "most", "was", ",", "``", "There", "'s", "a", "choice", "we", "'re", "making", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "Bob, you have nothing to worry about, OK?", "question_tokens": ["Bob", ",", "you", "have", "nothing", "to", "worry", "about", ",", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "Lionel, this has been one of my favorite interviews I've ever done at CNN.", "answer_tokens": ["Lionel", ",", "this", "has", "been", "one", "of", "my", "favorite", "interviews", "I", "'ve", "ever", "done", "at", "CNN", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "What's the word again?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "word", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "Swathed.", "answer_tokens": ["Swathed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 742, "question": "Hank, you're getting a bit of flak for this book and what was the purpose in writing it?", "question_tokens": ["Hank", ",", "you", "'re", "getting", "a", "bit", "of", "flak", "for", "this", "book", "and", "what", "was", "the", "purpose", "in", "writing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 743, "answer": "Well, you know, any time you're around greatness like I was for six years and you see it at close quarters, you're asked about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "any", "time", "you", "'re", "around", "greatness", "like", "I", "was", "for", "six", "years", "and", "you", "see", "it", "at", "close", "quarters", ",", "you", "'re", "asked", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hank"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 753, "question": "I mean as far as coach and player goes, it doesn't get much closer than that, does it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "as", "far", "as", "coach", "and", "player", "goes", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "get", "much", "closer", "than", "that", ",", "does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "Well, I mean, that's a lot of time to spend with a player.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "time", "to", "spend", "with", "a", "player", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "What do you make of him as a man?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "him", "as", "a", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "Well, I mean, very complex.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "very", "complex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 766, "question": "How do you respond to that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "respond", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 767, "answer": "Well, I'm certainly not the first coach that's ever written a book.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "certainly", "not", "the", "first", "coach", "that", "'s", "ever", "written", "a", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 782, "question": "What's your response to him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "response", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 783, "answer": "Well, I mean, those rules are not, you know, written rules.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "those", "rules", "are", "not", ",", "you", "know", ",", "written", "rules", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 795, "question": "Did you just think, you know what in the guy let me down, he wasn't a proper friend to me so I'm going to make money out of his intimate life and the way that you have done?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "just", "think", ",", "you", "know", "what", "in", "the", "guy", "let", "me", "down", ",", "he", "was", "n't", "a", "proper", "friend", "to", "me", "so", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "make", "money", "out", "of", "his", "intimate", "life", "and", "the", "way", "that", "you", "have", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 796, "answer": "No, not in any way, shape or form.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "in", "any", "way", ",", "shape", "or", "form", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tiger"], "PERSON": ["Mark Steinberg"]}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "Could you quite believe what you were hearing when all these stories began to come out?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "quite", "believe", "what", "you", "were", "hearing", "when", "all", "these", "stories", "began", "to", "come", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "No, I couldn't, because the first, you know, inkling that there might be a problem was Mark Steinberg, Tiger's agent called me, and told me that there was going to be an article coming out in the \"National Enquirer\" but that it wasn't true.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "could", "n't", ",", "because", "the", "first", ",", "you", "know", ",", "inkling", "that", "there", "might", "be", "a", "problem", "was", "Mark", "Steinberg", ",", "Tiger", "'s", "agent", "called", "me", ",", "and", "told", "me", "that", "there", "was", "going", "to", "be", "an", "article", "coming", "out", "in", "the", "``", "National", "Enquirer", "''", "but", "that", "it", "was", "n't", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Williams"]}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 823, "question": "Would you have done if you'd known?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "done", "if", "you", "'d", "known", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 824, "answer": "I don't think it would be my place necessarily as a coach, but it would be my place I feel like as a friend, and I certainly would have said something, and I know Steve Williams would have said something, too.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "would", "be", "my", "place", "necessarily", "as", "a", "coach", ",", "but", "it", "would", "be", "my", "place", "I", "feel", "like", "as", "a", "friend", ",", "and", "I", "certainly", "would", "have", "said", "something", ",", "and", "I", "know", "Steve", "Williams", "would", "have", "said", "something", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 826, "question": "Do you feel that he's changed at all since the scandal?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "he", "'s", "changed", "at", "all", "since", "the", "scandal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 827, "answer": "You know, I think he's probably softened some.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "probably", "softened", "some", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 833, "question": "Could he win the Masters this year, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "he", "win", "the", "Masters", "this", "year", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 834, "answer": "Well, he's definitely striking the ball well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "definitely", "striking", "the", "ball", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]